internettraffic247.com 2019-01-18

# Traffic Speedway

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy details how Traffic Speedway uses and protects any information that you give Traffic Speedway when you use this website.

Traffic Speedway is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Traffic Speedway may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you agree.

**Information Collected**

In order to use this service a person must register using his or her contact information such as your name, email address and IP address. This information is used to login to use our service and to contact the member regarding our service and or products. Upon registration and each login your IP address is recorded. We use this information to provide our services and features to you, to improve those services, and to provide you with customer support. We also gather statistics on how many ads you view, how many prizes you win or what earnings you make.

**Security**

We take every precaution to protect our members information. The site offers high security SSL login and encryption on ever page where personal details are added. Only the administrator of this website has access to members email address and other information. We do NOT sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Members right to cancel**

All members of Traffic Speedway have a right to cancel their account at any time. Simply send a support ticket saying you want to delete your account, and your account and all information will be permanently removed from our site.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, Traffic Speedway cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

**Controlling your personal information**

A member, at any time, may go to their account information and update their information.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns or comments about our privacy policy you can contact us by opening a support ticket on the "Support" page or sending an email to: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)com
